--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://www.cmct.cc
影片压制：死亡骑士　字幕调校：鬼畜职人　招募Q号：76846146
片名：急速天劫
民众应当了解 即使把所有联邦预算都用在安防上
People have to realize,we cannot make everybody totally safe,
我们也不可能让所有人都绝对安全
even if we allocated the entire federal budget towards security.
我向你们保证 在整个联邦政府中…
I promise you there is not an easier job...
最惬意的工作 莫过于坐在头等舱里…
in the whole federal government than riding first class in airplanes from...
喂
Yeah.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
不 你可以信任我 我没事
No,no,you can trust me. I'm fine.
什么？我听不清
What? I can't hear you.
我听不清
I can't hear you!
嘿 有火吗？
Hey,man,you got a light?
先生 打扰一下
Sir. Excuse me.
打扰一下 你有火吗？
Excuse me,sir. You got a light?
有 对不起
Yeah. Sorry.
各位乘客请注意
May I have your attention,please?
你到哪去？
So,where you off to?
你要去哪啊？
Where you headed?
我要去阿姆斯特丹
I'm headed to Amsterdam.
各位乘客请注意
May I have your attention,please?
白色区域只允许马上登机的旅客通过
The white zone is for the immediate loading
或刚下机的旅客通过
and unloading of passengers only.
给 先生 祝你一路愉快
Here you go,sir. Enjoy your flight.
所有人现在都在关心
Everyone and their mother's in the game right now.
什么韩国手机 日本手机 斯堪的纳维亚手机
You got Korean phones,Japanese phones,Scandinavian phones.
操作系统还得跟上15个不同厂家的硬件更新
OS is trying to keep up with the hardware from 15 different manufacturers.
对
Right!
我一直就是这个意思 没人听我的
That's what I've been saying. No one listens to me!
哥们 你这是班门弄斧了 完全不必跟我说这些
Dude,you're preaching to the choir! It makes absolutely no sense.
没搞错？看来我挡了你的路
Really? I guess I'm in your way.
这些纽约人啊 给我两分钟
New Yorkers,man,I swear to God. Give me two minutes.
可以了
Clear.
请这里来 先生
Right this way,sir. Please.
听我说 我不能在伦敦停留3天
Listen to me. Listen to me. I cannot stay in London for three days.
给我安排最快的航班回来
Get me on the next flight back.
拜托 听我说 这…
Please,look. This is...
现在时间不合适…
This is a bad time for...
"你是不得已的" 你猜怎么着？我也是
"You have to do what you have to do." Well,guess what? So do I.
给
Here.
长途飞行是最糟糕的
Long flights are the worst.
不了 谢谢
No,thanks.
嗨 亲爱的
Hi,baby.
晚上好 乘客们
Good evening,passengers.
我的预订出了问题
There's a mix-up with my reservation.
我本该是靠窗的座位 他们却给我安排了靠过道的
I was supposed to have a window seat and they put me in an aisle.
也许你可以调调座位
Maybe you could move some people around,
因为我订的是靠窗座位
'cause I was guaranteed the window seat.
对不起了 萨默斯太太
I'm sorry about that,Ms. Summers.
我们请带孩子的乘客
At this time we are inviting passengers with small children,
或是需要协助的乘客 此时登机
or who require assistance,to board at this time.
重复一遍 在登机区
Once again,in the boarding area,
飞往伦敦的10次航班开始优先乘客登机
we are ready to begin our priority boarding Flight 10 to London.
几分钟后将开始普通乘客登机
We'll begin general boarding in just a few minutes.
你们都准备好登机了吗？
Are you all set to board?
我们必须去跑道上？
So we have to go on the runway?
来 孩子 行李都在里面了？
Come on,sweetheart. Is this everything?
是的 我妈妈为我检查了大包
Yeah. My mom checked my big bag for me.
你以前自己坐过飞机吗？
Have you flown by yourself before?
没有 这是我第一次
No. This is my first time.
你会过得很愉快的
You're gonna have a lovely time.
欢迎登机 只需要穿过这里 然后左拐
Welcome aboard. Yes,just through there and down to the left.
南希 这是贝嘉 这是她第一次坐飞机
Nancy,this is Becca. It's her first time on an airplane.
很好 谁在伦敦等你？
Wonderful. Who's waiting for you in London?
我爸爸
My dad.
我们已经为你选择了靠窗座位
Well,we've a seat by the window all picked out for you.
我知道看起来很可怕 但是飞行是很有乐趣的
Look,I know it may seem scary,but flying's really quite fun.
这个小家伙逃走了吧
I believe this little guy made a run for it.
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
亨利
Henry.
他长相适合这名字 是个好名字
Yeah,he looks like a Henry. That's a good name.
- 那么… - 贝嘉
- Well... - Becca.
贝嘉 我觉得亨利有点害怕
Becca,I think Henry's a little scared.
也许你能为他做个榜样
Maybe you can show him how it's done.
好孩子
Good girl.
抱歉 我挡了你的路？
I'm sorry,am I in your way?
又一次？
Again?
我们就在这里
We are right up here.
晚上好 各位乘客
Good evening,ladies and gentlemen.
在此提醒 所有手提行李必须塞在舱顶行李箱
As a reminder,all carry-on luggage must fit in the overhead bin
或是安全的塞在您面前的座位下
or be safely stowed under the seat in front of you.
如果行李塞不进去
If you're having trouble fitting your luggage,
我们愿帮您寄存
we'll be happy to check it for you.
谢谢您选择英国亚奎兰蒂航空公司航班 祝旅途愉快
Thank you for choosing British Aqualantic. Enjoy the flight.
请问这个座位有人吗？
Do you know,is there somebody sitting there?
- 这是谁的座位？- 不知道 对不起
- Do you know who has that seat? - No,sorry.
这里有人吗？
Is somebody sitting here?
嘿 我在飞机上 你猜怎么着？他们搞错了我的预订
Hey,I'm on the plane. And guess what? They effed up my reservation.
7:35抵达 他们预订汽车了吗？
We land at 7:35. Did they book a car?
等一下
Hang on. Hang on.
打扰一下 先生 我的座位号是3B
Excuse me. Sir? I'm here in 3B.
请问能不能和你换下座位？
I was wondering if maybe you'd switch seats
让我好靠窗坐
with me so I could have the window?
你在意吗？
Do you care?
你会说英语吗？
Do you speak English?
好 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
打扰一下 先生
Excuse me. Excuse me. Sir?
你好 我的座位在这里 3B
Hi. I'm right here,I'm in 3B
请问你是否更愿意坐在靠过道的座位
and I was just wondering if maybe you would prefer the aisle,
或者坐在哪里都无所谓
or if you don't care,if you would
能不能和我换换座位？
switch with me for the window seat?
很多人都是睡一路 我想问问…
A lot of people just sleep anyway,so I was wondering if...
好的 换就换
Sure. Why not?
太谢谢了 非常感谢
Thank you so much. I really appreciate that.
对不起 我先让一下
Sorry,let me get out of your way.
让我帮你
Let me help you.
这里有地方
There's room right up here.
亚奎兰蒂航空公司愿意提供广泛的机上娱乐节目
Aqualantic is pleased to offer extensive in-flight entertainment
可以方便的订阅数百份影视和音乐节目
with hundreds of video and music programming at your fingertips.
天啊
Oh,God.
喂 你在吗？
Hello? Are you there?
你的手机
Your phone.
- 什么？- 喂
- What? - Hello?
- 你的手机 - 该死
- Your phone. - Oh,shit.
- 喂？- 嗨 嗨
- Hello? - Hi. Hi,hi.
我下飞机再联系你 好吗？再见
I'll call you when we land,okay? All right,bye.
今天不顺心吗？
Rough day,huh?
是啊 别提了
Yeah,you have no idea.
你好 打扰一下
Hi,excuse me.
方便的话 给我拿杯奎宁杜松子酒可以吗？
Could I get a gin and tonic,when you get a chance?
- 好的 - 我也要一杯 谢谢
- Of course. - Make that two,please.
天啊
God.
- 你叫南希 对吧？我叫格温 - 是的
- Nancy,right? Gwen. - Yeah.
感谢上帝
Thank God for you.
她没来 只留下我一人
Girl doesn't show up and leaves me
服务两个客舱 你帮了大忙
to handle two cabins. You're a lifesaver.
假如我晕过去了 请务必在我摔倒前扶住我
If I pass out,just promise to catch me before I hit the floor.
除非是我先晕过去
Not if I do first.
起飞前你们还需要什么吗？
Can I get you gentlemen anything before we taxi?
不用了 南希
No,thanks,Nance,I'm fine.
怎么了？
What?
没什么
Nothing.
控制塔 我是AQ-10次航班 准备断开地面电源
Ground,this is AQ-10,we're ready to disconnect ground power.
你这流氓
You naughty boy.
流氓
Naughty.
谢谢
Thank you.
你不是点了奎宁杜松子酒吗？
Didn't you order gin and tonic?
是吗？
Did I?
她给你拿了矿泉水
'Cause she brought you a water.
今天我不走运
It's not my lucky day.
- 情况如何 - 正常
晚上好 各位乘客
Good evening,ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎乘坐英国亚奎兰蒂航空公司10次航班 直达伦敦
welcome aboard British Aqualantic Flight 10,non-stop service to London.
我是机长大卫·麦克米伦
I'm your captain,David McMillan,
和副驾驶员凯尔·赖斯一起驾驶
flying with First Officer Kyle Rice.
预计今夜一路顺风
And we expect a smooth ride this evening
- 飞行时间约6小时多 - 请系好安全带 谢谢
- with a flight time of just over six hours. - Seatbelts,thank you.
我们很快就将起飞
We should have you in the air momentarily.
她的这张照片很漂亮
This is a beautiful picture they took of her.
先生 能否把靠背向前的？谢谢
Sir,could you move your seat-back forward? Thank you.
乘务人员 请坐好准备起飞
Flight attendants,please be seated for takeoff.
为何这么做 图个吉利？
What's that for? Is that for luck?
差不多 是我女儿给我的
Something like that. My daughter gave it to me.
肯定比奎宁杜松子酒强
Better than a gin and tonic,I bet.
是的
It is.
我叫珍妮
I'm Jen.
我叫比尔
Bill.
- 你乘飞机次数多吗？- 经常乘飞机
- You fly much? - All the time,actually.
能看出来
Yeah,I can tell.
只是起飞时紧张 等升空之后 我就…
It's just the takeoff. Once we're in the air,I'll...
你就癫痫发作？
You'll have a seizure?
我没事的 真的
I'll be fine. I promise.
你真的经常乘飞机？
You actually fly all the time?
有些事情永远习惯不了
Some things you never get used to.
你女儿多大了？
How old's your daughter?
如今17岁了
Now,she's,uh,17.
她叫什么名字？
What's her name?
奥利维亚
Olivia.
- 不错 - 是啊
- That's nice. - Yeah.
我喜欢这名字 是个好名字
I like that name,it's a nice name.
她为何给你这个丝带？
So,Why'd she give you the ribbon?
有些小孩子喜欢毛毯 动物玩具 奥利维亚喜欢丝带
Some kids have blankets,stuffed animals. Olivia had ribbons.
在她小时候 这曾是她的
This was hers when she was little.
她睡觉前常把它绑在手指或脚趾上
She'd tie it to a finger or toe before going to bed.
第二天早上醒来 她会让我猜
And then in the morning,she'd make me guess.
- 猜绑在哪里？- 没错
- Where she put it? - Yeah.
真可爱 好可爱啊
That's cute. That's really cute.
是啊 然后她长大了
Yeah,and then she grew up.
可能我比她更需要它
I suppose I need it more than she did.
就这样
anyway
你是什么做职业的？
So,what do you do for a living?
呃…
Well...
我经常出差
I fly a lot.
是吗？
Oh. yeah?
是啊 不过我觉得
Yeah,but I think that
我想睡上一觉
I'm gonna try to get some sleep.
- 睡一觉 当然 - 是啊 这一路很长
- Get some sleep,sure. - Yeah,it's gonna be a long flight.
是啊 睡个好觉
Yeah,yeah,yeah. Sleep well.
- 放手 - 宝贝…
- Stop! - Baby...
- 你疯了 - 你这么美 我控制不住自己
- You're crazy! - You're so hot,baby,I can't stop it! I can't!
别人看着呢
People are watching!
没人在看
No,no,no. Nobody's watching. Nobody.
噢 我的天啊
Oh,my God.
当着我妈的面 他没穿裤子
In front of my mom,with no pants on
嘴里还含着半块巧克力
and half a Toblerone in his mouth.
不是吧
He didn't.
你认识他吗？
Do you know him?
美国空警
准备好尽你的职责了吗？空警
你是谁
你的一个乘客
侵入该网络是违法的
在卫生间吸烟也是违法的
现在能认真听我说了吗？
把手表的闹钟设置在20分钟后
为什么
因为在整整20分钟后
我要杀了飞机上的一个人
你想要什么
1.5亿美元
存入此帐户 CH10 00230 00A10982
我哪有这个本事
你这人足智多谋
喝一杯
想想办法
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你们有什么样的茶呢？
What kind of tea do you have?
我要甘菊茶 谢谢
I'll have chamomile. Thanks.
好的
Certainly.
20分钟内确认到账
否则还会死个人
然后以此类推
- 有你这么开玩笑的吗？- 你胡说什么？
- This your idea of a joke? - What're you talking about?
如果对我有意见 当着我的面说
If you have a problem with me,say it to my face.
不要在飞机上 在保安网络中玩游戏
Don't play games on a flight in a secure network.
请你冷静 拍档
You need to calm down,partner.
我当了25年警察 我了解你这种人
I was a cop for 25 years. I knew men like you.
我这种人？
Men like me?
我这样的人循规蹈矩
Men like me follow goddamn protocol.
我们现在不该交谈的
We're not even supposed to be talking right now.
这是保安网络 杰克
It's a secure network,Jack!
比尔 你到底在说什么？
Bill,what the hell are you talking about?
不要否认是你发送的
Don't deny you sent these.
比尔 不是我发送的
Bill,I didn't send these.
你自己看
See for yourself.
哈蒙德特工 你在AQ10次航班上
知道了 谢谢
情况如何
正常
那么飞机上有人威胁杀一名乘客
Then someone on this flight is threatening to kill a passenger
除非在18分钟内转账1.5亿美元
unless $150 million is transferred in the next 18 minutes.
谁知道这事？
Who knows about this?
你和我
You and me.
我看不可能 这是扯淡
I say no way. It's bullshit.
任何对飞机的威胁都要紧急降落
Any threat to an aircraft requires immediate landing.
好 假如有威胁
Right,yeah,all right. If there is a threat.
拜托 比尔 难道你希望
Come on,Bill. You wanna be the agent
让国际航班迫降
who lands an international flight
就因为某个混蛋知道你的个人缺点？
because some asshole knows your personal problems?
给你发几个笑话短信？
Sends you a couple of joke texts?
比尔 我得问你 你今天喝了多少？
Bill,I gotta ask you,how many have you had today?
威胁都要认真对待
A threat's a threat!
好
Okay.
我们要把这事考虑清楚 拍档 好吗？
You really need to think this through,partner,all right?
怎么可能在飞机上杀人
Listen,how do you kill somebody aboard
又能逃之夭夭呢？
a crowded plane and get away with it?
很难办到这一点 不是吗？
Pretty hard to pull that off,don't you think?
如果没有情况 你就不要制造情况
Bill,if there's not a situation,you don't create one.
我去找机长
I'm going to see the captain.
你盯着主舱
You keep your eye on the main cabin.
比尔 不要让驾驶舱惊慌 比尔
Bill? Don't panic the cockpit. Bill?
真的 过了5个小时
I tell you,it's five hours in
然后突然之间 他就站起来说…
and then,out of nowhere,he suddenly sits up and he says...
- 我们如何核实这一威胁呢？- 核实不了
- How do we validate the threat? - We can't.
机长 运输安全局说 全面调查登机乘客
Captain? TSA says a full cross check on the passenger manifest
可能需要25-30分钟
could take 25 to 30 minutes.
假如确有其事 我们可以改换航线
We can divert the flight,if this is for real.
最近的机场在哪？
The nearest airport?
已经离开哈利法克斯95分钟
Well,it's 95 minutes back to Halifax,
距冰岛两小时 伦敦三小时
two hours to Iceland,three to London.
我们正在大西洋中间
We're midway over the Atlantic.
你没事吧？
You okay?
我正在节食 手经常发抖
It's this juice fast I'm on. Gives me the shakes.
决定权在你 比尔
It's your call,Bill.
这算是威胁情况吗？
Do we have a situation?
能看一下录像吗？
Can we review the footage?
这是录制在黑匣子中
It's recorded directly to the black box.
在餐间可以看实时监控吧？
But I can watch all the camera feeds live from the galley?
是的
Yeah.
继续和运输安全局联系
Get back on the line with TSA.
看看他们能否追踪这一账号
See if they can back trace this account number.
在此期间 我也需要乘客名单
In the meantime,I'll need the passenger manifest.
看看能不能找到他
I'll see if I can find him.
但10分钟后 我要你切断网络
But in 10 minutes,I'd like you to switch off the network system.
我们不能让他查看是否已经转账
We don't want him checking to see if a transfer's been made.
南希 跟我来
Nancy,come with me.
商务舱有两个摄像头 经济舱有6个
Two cameras in business,six in coach.
我们还需要人监控
We're gonna need more eyes.
我再找个乘务员
I'll get another attendant.
你对乘务人员有多熟悉？
How well do you know the crew?
不很熟
Not very well.
- 打扰一下 - 什么？
- Excuse me. - Yeah?
请跟我来一下
Will you come with me,please?
可以吗？
Now?
你要我现在就去？
You want me to come right now?
这样不好
This is a bad idea.
这事开始的时候 她就坐在我旁边
She was sitting beside me when this started.
这飞机上我唯一信任的就是你和她
The only two people I trust on this airplane are you and her.
信任我什么？出了什么事？
Trust me with what? What's going on?
我发短信 你们圈出拿手机的乘客
I text,you circle any passenger with a phone
或像是拿着手机的人
or acting like they have a phone.
我不明白你要我干什么…
I'm not sure I understand what it is you want me to do...
拜托 就按我说的做
Please,just do as I ask.
你在吗？
我有个难题
各位乘客 看来…
Ladies and gentlemen,looks like
我们遇到一些意外的气流
we've hit some unexpected turbulence.
请回到各自座位上 系上安全带
Please return to your seats and keep your seatbelts fastened
你转账了没有？
直到在机舱内可以安全走动 谢谢
until it's safe to move about the cabin. Thank you.
你转账了没有？
我还需要些时间
我们正在找航空公司的老板
那里 9B
There. 9B.
你在浪费时间
座位号9B 大卫·诺顿
Seat 9B. David Norton.
我不是航空公司员工 不在乎他们的钱
我只负责乘客的安全
你是个好人 比尔
22C座位
22C.
你为何这么做
奥斯汀·雷利
Austin Reilly.
- 你为何要这么做 - 我有我的理由
什么理由
2F座位
2F.
詹森·科尔
Jason Cole.
什么理由
充分理由
14C座位
14C.
14C 查尔斯·维勒
14C,Charles Wheeler.
给我搞到钱 比尔
13B座位
13B.
法西姆·纳西尔
Fahim Nasir.
你时间不多了
5B座位
5B.
5B座位 爱丽丝·玛丽安
5B. Iris Marianne.
你该接电话
You better answer it.
喂
Hello?
为了救这些人 你愿做什么
比尔
Bill?
我愿不惜一切
比尔
Bill?
所以我才选择了你
- 你是谁？- 菲利普·麦尼克
- Who is this? - This is Philip Marenick.
运输安全局的 我听机长说你遇到情况
I'm with TSA. I understand from the captain you have a situation.
我要和我的上级谈
I need to speak to my supervisor.
我是在华盛顿的国土安全部打电话
Listen,I'm calling from the DHS here in D.C.
比尔 有人要死了
从现在起 我就是你的上级
From here on out,I am your supervisor.
马克斯特工 我需要你…
Now,Agent Marks,I need you...
我需要你调查几个座位号 告诉我危险人物和可疑人物
I'm going to run seat numbers by you. I need red flags and priors.
- 你这个要求很严肃 - 20G座位
- That's a very serious request you put in. - 20G.
马克斯特工 我要你跟我
Agent Marks,I need you to take me
讲讲整个事情经过
through the events from the beginning.
我们正调查你给我们的账号
And we're looking into tracing the account number you gave us.
又是20G
20G again.
你知道 在这种情况下 按规定…
And as you know,protocol dictates in these situations...
你还剩不到5分钟
我们要和机上第二空警核实
we corroborate everything with the second officer on board.
还是20G
20G again.
不是他
It's not him.
不是谁？听着 我宁愿不要急于下结论
It's not who? Look,I'd rather not jump to any conclusions.
我有个问题一直想问你
比尔 你目前不适合
Listen,Bill,I don't think you're in a position to sort out
判断谁是嫌疑犯 谁不是
who's a suspect or not at this point.
你女儿好吗？
马克斯特工
Agent Marks?
比尔
Bill?
奥利维亚怎样了？比尔
马克斯特工 我需要你表示服从
Agent Marks,I need some sort of acknowledgment from you.
比尔
Bill?
马克斯特工
Agent Marks?
马克斯 你要回复我
Marks,you need to answer me.
等一下
Hang on.
马克斯 你在吗？
Marks,are you there?
回到你的座位上
Go back to your seat.
你这混蛋
You son-of-a-bitch!
小点声
Keep your voice down.
- 交出来 - 你说什么...
- Hand it over! - What're you...
比尔 看着我 我需要这笔钱
Bill,look at me,okay? I need this money.
可以分给你一份…
I can cut you in...
- 给我手机 杰克 - 听我说
- Give me the goddamn phone,Jack. - Just listen to me.
给我手机…
Give me the phone...
杰克 你这混蛋
Jack! You son-of-a-bitch.
- 放手 马克斯 - 住手
- Give it up,Marks. - Stop it!
- 放手 - 住手
- Give it up. - Stop it.
该死的 杰克
Damn it,Jack!
住手 住手
Stop it. Stop it!
别打了
Stop fighting!
杰克
Jack!
别这么做 杰克
Don't do this,Jack.
住手
Stop it!
不要
Don't.
别这样
别这么做 杰克
Don't do this,Jack!
不要
Don't!
很遗憾你必须下手 比尔
重新设置你的表
只有一个办法能停止此事
给我弄到钱
否则还有人会死去
你所保护的人
谁知道你下一个会害死谁呢
各位乘客 我是机长
Ladies and gentlemen,this is your captain speaking.
我为带来的不便表示歉意…
I apologize for the inconvenience...
该死
Shit.
我们目前网络中断
but our network is down for the moment.
请稍等一下 我们会试图重启网络
If you just bear with us,we'll attempt to restart the Internet.
- 恢复网络 - 什么？
- Turn the network back on. - What?
打开网络
The network,turn it on.
我们会继续通知你们
We'll keep you posted.
我需要重启网络
I need the network system back on.
你去吧 南希
Go ahead,Nance.
你给我们的账号
The account number you gave us.
是在你的名下
It's in your name.
什么？
What?
运输安全局刚核实了
TSA just confirmed it.
怎么会这样
That doesn't make any sense.
你了解我 你知道我绝不会…
You know me. You know I'd never do...
我知道 我知道
I know,I know.
20分钟时间已到 出什么事了吗？
Look,the 20 minutes are up. Has anything happened?
没有
No.
可能只是恶作剧
It's probably just a hoax.
对航空公司发泄不满
Some elaborate middle finger to the airline industry.
打扰一下 你在等着进去吗？
Excuse me. Are you waiting?
没有 你去吧
No. Go ahead.
特工…
Agent...
你好 女士
Hi,ma'am.
和你通过电话的麦尼克特工
Agent Marenick,who you spoke with,
会在华盛顿继续调查
will continue to handle the investigation from D.C.
大卫…
David...
他们也让我收走你的警徽和手枪
And they've asked me to take your badge and your gun.
- 不 - 比尔
- No. - Bill.
- 不 - 比尔…
- No. - Bill...
我没别的选择
I don't have a choice here.
我是空警
I'm the air marshal.
- 比尔… - 好吧 好吧
- Bill... - Okay. Okay.
你去坐下 放松
Look,just sit back,relax,
- 然后… - 享受旅程
- and... - Enjoy the flight.
对 享受旅程
Enjoy the flight,yeah.
是他吗？20G座位上的那人
Was it him? The guy in 20G?
不是 没什么
No,it was nothing.
我不小心把手机掉在水池里了
I dropped my stupid phone in the sink.
天啊 我也经常这样
Oh,God,I do that all the time.
半年里损失了5部手机
I lost like five phones in six months,
然后我学会一个小窍门
and then I learned this little trick.
就好了
Here we go.
那我还需要担心吗？
So,should I be worried?
不 完全不必
No,not at all.
不该把你卷入进来 对不起
It was a mistake to involve you,I'm sorry.
既然不是他 为何他的手机在你手上？
So,if it's not him,then why do you have his phone?
为了万无一失 即便
I have to be careful,even when
没什么可担心的
there's nothing to be concerned about.
这是我的职责
It's my job.
身为乘客 我不是有权知道发生什么事吗？
As a passenger,don't I have the right to know what's going on?
- 听我说… 你叫珍妮 是吧？- 是的
- Listen... Jen,right? - Yeah.
只是个恶作剧 某个拿手机的年轻人
It's an innocent prank. Some kid with a cell phone.
假如是在地面上 我立刻就能
If it was on the ground,I'd catch him
抓住他 但在飞机上
in two seconds flat,but up here,
500英里的时速 我无法追踪他的手机
traveling at 500 miles an hour,I can't track his phone.
没什么办法
There's nothing I can do.
没什么办法？你不是空警吗？
There's nothing you can do? Aren't you an air marshal?
女士 请回到座位上
Ma'am,please return to your seat.
你叫我"女士"？
Did you just call me "ma'am"?
请回到座位上
Please return to your seat.
没搞错？你叫我"女士"？
Seriously? Did you call me "ma'am"?
马上
Now.
好 比尔
Okay,Bill.
我去就是
I'm going.
- 谢谢配合 - 我去
- Thank you. - Ugh.
哈蒙德特工你好
你是谁?
你的守护天使，你要乖乖听我的话
朋友 你可是和特工的在玩啊
我知道你是什么样的人 哈蒙德
你找错人了
找的就是你 没错
我知道你的公文包里的东西
你怎么知道的
到飞机后面见我
快点
哈蒙德特工
Agent Hammond?
等一下
Just a moment.
南希
Nancy.
对不起 指示器肯定出故障了
Sorry. The indicator must be broken.
我本来是找哈蒙德特工
I was looking for Agent Hammond.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
南希 等等 等等
Nancy,wait. Wait!
南希 拜托
Nancy,please.
冷静 冷静
Calm down,calm down.
冷静
Calm down.
拜托 你听我解释
Please,I can explain this.
好吗？
Okay?
这是个圈套
This is a setup.
机长刚才告诉我
The captain just told me that the account
他们要求的账号是在我的名下
they want the money wired to is in my name.
难道我会用我名下的账户
Do you think I would extort $150 million
敲诈1.5亿美元？
using an account in my own name?
他在走私可卡因 南希
He was transporting cocaine,Nancy.
我们调查的人知道这一点
Whoever we're looking for knew that.
他威胁哈蒙德 让他心神不定
He threatened Hammond,made him paranoid.
我发现之后 哈蒙德想杀了我
I found out,and Hammond tried to kill me.
做这件事的人 希望造成这种假象
The person who's doing this,he wants it to look like this.
好像这事是两个联邦特工干的 而不是他
Like two federal agents are the ones doing this,not him.
杰克拿枪对着我 我没别的选择
Jack pulled a gun on me. I had no choice.
南希
Nancy?
我没别的选择
I had no choice.
你了解我
You know me.
你知道我绝不会做出这种事
You know I could never do something like this.
看着我
Look at me.
我需要你相信我
I need you to believe me.
我相信你
I believe you.
13分钟后 还有人会死 除非我先找到他
In 13 minutes,someone else will die,unless I find him first.
我需要你帮我
I need you to help me.
各位乘客请注意
Ladies and gentlemen,may I have your attention,please?
我叫比尔·马克斯
My name is Bill Marks.
我是驻本航班的空警
I'm the federal air marshal assigned to this flight.
对不起打扰了
I apologize for the disturbance.
运输安全局最近出台一项规定
The TSA has recently instituted a policy
可以随机搜查国际航班的乘客
of random searches aboard international flights.
遗憾的是 这是本月中的三次航班之一
Unfortunately,this is one of three lucky flights this month.
我将穿过机舱
I'm gonna be coming through the cabin.
如果我喊到你的名字和座位号
If I call your name and seat number,
请站起来 走到过道上
please stand up and move into the aisle.
如果你持有违禁品或武器
If you're in possession of an illegal substance,item or weapon,
最好现在就站出来
it's best to just step forward now.
机长 你来听听这个
Captain,you might want to hear this.
我要大家都把双手放在前面座位上
I need everybody to place both hands on the seat in front of you.
他妈的在干什么？
What the hell is he doing?
马上
Right now!
联系运输安全局 告诉他们我们可能遭遇劫机
Contact TSA,tell them we have a possible hijacking.
- 南希 怎么了？- 只是随机搜查
- Nancy,what's going on? - It's just a random search.
谢谢
Thank you.
借过
Excuse me.
珍妮·萨默斯
Jennifer Summers?
要不要告诉你我包里的炸弹？
Should I have told you about the bomb in my bag?
请不要在飞机上用这个词
Let's not use that word on a plane,please.
等我去了主舱之后 你盯着商务舱
When I move on to the main cabin,you watch business class.
如果看到任何可疑情况
If you see anything suspicious,
任何情况 就引起我的注意
anything at all,get my attention.
- 必要的话就喊叫 - 好
- Scream,if you have to. - Okay.
美国神经病
American paranoia.
爱丽丝·玛丽安 座位号5B 请站起来
Iris Marianne,5B. Stand up,please.
长者都是这么勾引年轻女子的吗？
Is that how older men pick up younger women?
先摸一遍 然后再聊？
Fondle first,talk later?
手机
Phone.
为什么不把你的号码输进去？
Why don't you enter your number?
你对我来说太年轻了
You're a little young for me.
这人以为自己是谁啊
Who does this guy think he is?
没事的 你冷静
It's all right. Just calm down!
- 刚结婚？- 昨天
- Just married? - Yesterday.
- 恭喜 - 谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
坐下
Sit down.
没什么担心的 这是常事
It's nothing to worry about. Happens all the time.
- 13B座位 法西姆·纳西尔 - 胡说
- 13B,Fahim Nasir. - Bullshit.
- 请起立 - 谢谢 先生
- Stand. - Thank you,sir.
感觉还好吗？
Feeling okay?
飞行不是我喜欢的
Flying is not my cup of tea.
谁说不是呢
Tell me about it.
- 你是个医生 - 你怎么知道的？
- You're a doctor. - How do you know?
能把你的包拿上来吗？
Your bag. Can you fetch it up,please?
好的 就在这儿
Sure. It's right down here.
哪个一科的医生？
What kind of doctor?
分子神经科学
Molecular neuroscience.
感觉很厉害
Sounds interesting.
喂 我们有人还要睡觉呢
Hey,look,man,some of us need to get some sleep.
先生 坐下 安静
Sir,sit down. Be quiet.
14C 查尔斯·维勒？站起来
14C,Charles Wheeler? Stand.
他的包里什么也没有？
There was nothing in his bag?
你此行目的是什么？
What's the purpose of your trip?
我在英国有个当事人 我是破产律师
I have a client in Brighton. I'm a bankruptcy attorney.
是吗？水平高吗？
Yeah? You any good?
- 怎么 你需要个律师？- 坐下
- Why? Oh,you need one? - Sit down.
先生 你要把手放在前面座位上 谢谢
Sir,you need to keep your hands on the seat in front of you. Thank you.
真是的
This sucks.
真是荒唐 接下来搜查我们？
This is crazy. Are we next?
放松
Just relax.
好 22C 奥斯汀·雷利 站起来
Okay,22C. Austin Reilly. Stand.
你能接着往前走吗？真是的
Hey,look. Can we move this along? Seriously,man.
我不会对你说第二遍
I'm not gonna tell you again.
雷利先生 你是做什么职业的？
Mr. Reilly,what do you do for a living?
纽约警察局的
NYPD.
伦敦是你的目的地？
London your final destination?
我的宝贝弟弟要和一个英国口音的男人结婚了
My fairy brother's getting married to a guy with a British accent.
我能看看你的手机吗？
Mind if I take a look at your phone?
拜托 没搞错？
Come on,man. Are you serious'?
这也太欺负人了
This is some Big Brother-type shit.
坐下
Take your seat.
你 到过道上 快 站起来
You,step into the aisle. Come on,up!
马上站起来
UP! Right now!
不用了
Nah,man,I'm good.
必须站起来 摘掉墨镜
I'm not asking. Shades off.
拜托 现在有凌晨两点了吧？
Come on. What is it,like 2:00 a.m.?
你还是回去 让我接着睡吧 好吗？
Why don't you go back up there so I can go back to sleep,man?
- 墨镜 - 我不摘
- Shades. - No,dude!
拜托 别冲动
Come on,man! Yo,chill!
让我看看你的手机
Let me see your phone.
我没手机
I don't have a phone,man.
天啊
Jesus.
这不是你的？
This isn't yours?
我从未见过它
Man,I ain't never seen that before.
看起来很像你在登机口用过的那部
Looks a hell of a lot like the one you were using at the gate.
看看我右边的美女
真是胡闹
This is ridiculous.
坐下
Sit down.
荣幸之至
Gladly.
我们可以停止玩游戏了吗？
你不是去阿姆斯特丹吗？
What happened to Amsterdam?
我在伦敦有亲人
I'm connecting to London.
让我看看你的登机证 你叫什么名字？
Show me your boarding pass. What's your name?
汤姆·博文 怎么了？
Tom Bowen. Why?
你轻点
Man,take it easy.
走
Move!
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything!
我有权利
Look,I have rights!
过来
Come here.
- 麦尼克？- 马克斯 你他妈在这干什么？
- Marenick? - Marks,what the hell is going on there?
听我说 威胁是真实的
Listen to me. The threat is real.
我要你立即停止你正在做的事
I want you to stop doing whatever you're doing immediately.
我拘捕了一个嫌疑犯 我需要背景调查
I have a suspect in custody. I need a background check.
座位号24E 汤姆·博文
Seat 24E,Tom Bowen,B-O-W-E-N.
你非法制伏无辜乘客 马克斯
You have unlawfully subdued innocent passengers,Marks.
我没时间说这个
I don't have time for this.
你登机前给你的上级打电话 还威胁了他
You called your supervisor before the flight and threatened him.
- 什么？- 他不肯为你安排航班
- What'? - He wouldn't book you an overtime flight
你就说要做不得已的事
and you said you'd do what you had to do.
- 我没威胁任何人 - 是吗？马克斯
- I didn't threaten anyone. - Is that right? Marks?
我需要对汤姆·博文的全面调查 座位号24E
I need to run a full check on Tom Bowen,seat 24E.
- 马克斯 真是的 - 快 别浪费时间了
- Marks,damn you! - Now! You're wasting time.
马克斯特工 你现在被解除职责了 听见了吗？
Marks... Agent Marks,you are hereby relieved of duty. Do you hear me?
3分钟后 这架飞机上会死人 听见了吗？
In three minutes,someone on this plane is gonna die. Do you hear me?
博文是干净的 老天啊 他是个学校老师呢
Bowen is clean,Bill. He's a schoolteacher,for Christ's sake.
他在伦敦有家人
He has family in London.
飞机上的人都是干净的 只除了你
Everyone on that flight is clean. Everyone except you.
马克斯
Marks?
你说了阿姆斯特丹
You said Amsterdam.
我从未问你要去哪里
I never asked you where you were going.
你主动提供这一信息
You volunteered that information.
为什么要对联邦特工撒谎？
Why would you lie to a federal agent?
我并不知道你是联邦特工
Look,I didn't know you were a federal agent.
为什么要对陌生人说谎？
Why would you lie to a stranger?
你要么现在回答问题 要么降落后在联邦拘留所中回答
You can answer questions now,or in federal custody when we land.
好吧 真是的
Look. Okay,Jesus.
他说只要我问你去哪里 就给我100块钱
He said he'd give me $100 if I asked you where you were flying. Okay?
我不知自己为啥要说阿姆斯特丹
I don't know why I said Amsterdam.
我对天发誓 我并不知道你是空警
I swear to God,I didn't know you were a federal marshal.
- 胡说 - 我对天发誓
- Bullshit! - I swear to God!
他说他想耍弄一个朋友 你叫威尔 是吧？
He said he wanted to play a prank on his friend. Will,right?
比尔
Bill.
比尔 都一样 我是为了100块钱
Bill. Whatever,man. I did it for 100 bucks.
- 他是谁？- 我不知道
- Who was he? - I don't know!
他长什么样的？
What does he look like?
白人 褐色头发 欧洲口音 大约30-35岁…
He was white with brown hair,a European accent,like 30,35 years old...
- 他在这飞机上吗？- 不知道 我没看见他
- Is he on this plane? - I don't know,I didn't see him.
等我回来时 他没给我钱 他已经走了
When I went back,he didn't pay me,he was already gone.
- 看到他你能认出来吗？- 我不知道
- You'd know him if you saw him? - I don't know!
我没看见他上这架飞机 我发誓
I never saw him get on the plane,man,I swear!
帮我看一下
Humor me. Look!
该死的
God damn it!
来 看看
Come on,look.
没看到他
I don't see him.
看看
Look.
- 走 看看 - 该死的 我没看到他
- Come on,look! - God damn it! I don't see him!
- 在那里 - 哪里？
- Right there. - Where?
那里 那个戴眼镜的
Right there. The glasses.
过去 走
Come on,move.
真是疯了
This is crazy.
你 你 看着我
You! You. Look at me.
看着我 你叫什么名字？
Look at me! What's your name?
迈克 迈克·塔特
Michael. Michael Tate.
- 是不是？- 不是他
- Well? - It's not him.
- 你确定？- 是的 该死的 我确定
- You're sure? - Yeah,God damn it,I'm sure!
假如我见过他上这架飞机
Look,if I'd seen him get on the plane,
我肯定去向他要钱了
I would've gone and asked him for my money.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
南希 盯着商务舱
Nancy,watch business class.
转过身
Turn around.
- 你是认真的？- 别说话
- Are you serious? - Don't talk.
现在坐下
Now,sit down.
不要动
Don't move.
我可没说过要杀的是乘客
天啊
Oh,God.
南希
Nancy!
所有人留在各自座位上
Everybody remain in your seats.
各位乘客 请留在各自座位上
Ladies and gentlemen,please remain in your seats
系上安全带
and keep your seatbelts fastened.
各位乘客 请留在各自座位上
Ladies and gentlemen,please remain in your seats
系上安全带
and keep your seatbelts fastened.
南希 你没事吧？
Nancy,are you okay?
- 没事 - 你确定？
- Yeah. - You sure?
出什么事了？
What's happened?
他开始胸痛 然后就倒在操纵杆上了
He started having chest pains,then he just collapsed over the yoke!
快 醒醒
Come on,come on! Wake up!
- 坐下 - 刚才怎么回事？
- Sit down! - What the hell was that?
一切都在控制中
Everything's under control.
打扰一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
机长没事吧？
Is the captain okay?
- 纳西尔医生 - 我什么都没干…
- Dr. Nasir? - I didn't do anything,I...
跟我来 马上
Come with me,now.
空警 告诉我 这是怎么回事？
Marshal! Is someone gonna tell us what the hell is going on?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
喂 人们很害怕
Hey! People are scared!
我们有权知道你为何搜查我们
We have a right to know why you searched us.
为何这架飞机差点坠毁
Why this plane almost went down!
空警 咱俩要谈谈
Hey,Marshal,you and I are gonna have a conversation.
别一走了之
Don't you walk away from me.
医生 马上去驾驶舱
Doctor,cockpit,now!
你让这个人进驾驶舱？
You're letting that guy in the cockpit?
按我说的做 回到你的座位上
Here's what's gonna happen. You're gonna get back to your seat,
接着坐下 然后闭嘴
you're gonna sit down,and you're gonna shut up.
否则呢？
Or what?
我们都是警察
From one cop to another,
你知道的
you know.
我也无能为力
There was nothing I could do.
刚才很不错
你很善于浪费时间
你很快就没有乘客了
然后只剩下你和我
打扰一下 小姐 你坐在那个空警旁边
Excuse me,miss? You were sitting next to that guy,the marshal?
你知道出什么事了吗？
You know what's happening?
我一点不知道
I have no idea.
没有受到击打的迹象
There's no evidence of assault.
可能是中毒 引发过敏
It could be poison. Induced anaphylaxis.
- 什么？- 过敏性反应
- What? - Allergic reaction.
不解剖的话 我…
Without an autopsy,I...
对
Yeah.
医生 你能不能看看
Doctor,would you mind seeing
机舱内有没有乘客需要医疗救助？
if any of the passengers in coach need medical assistance?
这件事…
This...
不要跟别人说 拜托了
This stays between us. Please.
南希 跟他去
Nancy,go with him.
凯尔
Kyle.
凯尔 我和机长交谈之后 他离开过驾驶舱吗？
Kyle,did the captain leave the cockpit since I last spoke with him?
- 你呢？- 没有
- You? - No.
有人进来过吗？
Did anyone else enter?
没有
No.
他吃过或喝过什么吗？
Has he had anything to eat or drink?
没有
I don't think so.
你或者机长有任何原因打开这个门吗？
Have you or the captain had any reason to unlock this door?
当然没有
Of course not.
那么这20分钟时间里
So you and he were both alone here,
你和他单独在这里？
on the flight deck,for the past 20 minutes?
你这混蛋
You bastard.
别动情绪
Don't get emotional.
我动情绪？看看你自己
I'm getting emotional? Look at you!
赖斯 假如你对我有意见…
Rice,if you have a problem with me...
我有意见的是朋友死在我身边
I have a problem with my friend dying next to me.
我有意见的是
I have a problem with being accused
被指控谋杀 还有劫机
of not only murder,but also hijacking.
我没指控你劫机
I didn't accuse you of hijacking.
天啊 我听说了你的事 你的问题是缺钱
Christ,I've heard about you. About your problems with money.
还有酗酒 运输安全局
With drinking. TSA.
给一个疯子酒鬼发了一把枪和一个警徽
They gave a paranoid alcoholic a gun and a badge
还让他上了我的飞机
and they put him on my plane.
惨了
Brilliant.
你要打我吗？
You're gonna hit me?
别告诉… 嘿 你在干什么？
Don't tell... Hey! Hey! What are you doing?
在飞机安全降落前 绝不要打开舱门 可以？
This door stays locked until this plane lands safely. Okay?
- 麦尼克… - 马克斯 该死的 我不是告诉你…
- Marenick... - Marks,God damn it,I thought I told you...
机长死了
The captain's dead.
什么？
Excuse me?
驾驶舱是封锁的 从里面锁上的
The cockpit was secured,locked from the inside.
让我猜猜 你进去过吧 比尔
Let me guess,were you inside,Bill?
副驾驶员说他就在旁边倒下了
The co-pilot said the man just collapsed beside him.
应该是引发过敏 好像是这个词
It could be induced anaphylaxis,I think it's called.
引发… 你说什么呢？
Induced... What are you talking about?
或是下毒 我不知道怎么下的手
Poisoning,I don't know how.
只有他和副驾驶员两人 副驾驶员我是信任的
It was just he and the co-pilot,and the co-pilot,I trust.
暂时还信任
For now.
"暂时"？我对比没把握 比尔
"For now"? I don't know about this,Bill.
麦尼克 你需要转账这笔钱
Marenick,you need to transfer the money.
哈蒙德特工在哪？
Where is Agent Hammond?
我要把你说的事跟他核实一下
I need to corroborate everything you're telling us.
哈蒙德死了
Hammond's dead.
什么？
What?
- 他手提箱里有可卡因 - 老天啊
- He had cocaine in his carry-on. - Jesus Christ!
我质问他的时候 他拿出了枪
I confronted him,he pulled a gun.
- 你是认真的？- 麦尼克 转账这笔钱
- Are you serious? - Marenick. Transfer the money.
争取点时间 我会查出他的
Buy me time. I'll find him.
转账这笔钱
Transfer the money.
1.5亿美元转到你的账户？
$150 million into your account?
比尔 你真的要我这么做？
Is that something you're seriously asking me to do,Bill?
飞机一降落你就逮捕我 冻结账户 你转账就是
The moment we land,arrest me,freeze the funds. Just transfer it.
我不能这么做 比尔
I can't do that,Bill.
航空公司认为 支付赎金的话
The airline believes paying the demand
会造成无法挽回的先例
will set a dangerous and irreversible precedent.
真是的 飞机上有150个人呢
Christ,there are 150 people on this plane.
所以我纳闷你怎么还没切断网络
Which makes me wonder why you haven't cut the network.
150个人在恐慌中
You have 150 people panicking,
在我们尽力处理情况时 他们却在联系家人
contacting their families,while we're trying to handle the situation.
你把这事归因于乘客
You attribute all this to a passenger,
可你不能提供任何他存在的证据
but you can give me no proof he actually exists.
我不能切断网络 我需要和他联系
I won't cut the network. I need to communicate with this guy.
马克斯特工 我不能继续和你谈了
Then,Agent Marks,I can't continue talking to you.
你是什么意思？
What does that mean?
意思是我们不和恐怖分子谈判
It means we will not negotiate with a terrorist.
南希
Nancy.
乘务人员中还有谁有权进入驾驶舱？
Who else in the crew has access to the cockpit?
只有我
Just me.
你要看看我的手机吗？马克斯特工
Would you like to see my phone,Agent Marks?
你的面试是上午吗？
Is your interview in the morning?
是的 如果我们还能赶到的话
Yeah. If we ever make it there.
是啊 除非能着陆的话 对吧？
Yeah,if we ever land,right?
没错 不过应该不会…
Exactly. But it shouldn't...
对不起 我起来
I'm sorry. I'll get up.
不用 没关系的 扎克 这是比尔
No. Please,don't worry about it. Zack,this is Bill.
这是扎克
Bill,Zack.
我刚才和他聊 扎克告诉我
We were just talking and Zack was telling me
他是智能手机设计员
that he's a programmer for smart phones.
是吗？
Is that right?
是的 我上午要去佩奇公司面试
Yeah. I'm interviewing at Paige in the morning
应聘一个软件分析的职位
for a software analytics position.
技术上说 不算编程 不过…
Which,technically,isn't programming. But...
听着 我很抱歉之前像个混蛋…
Look,I'm sorry for being such an asshole earlier...
嗯 不过你是个程序员 对吧？
Yeah,but you were a programmer,right?
我告诉他我经常找不到手机
I was telling him that I keep losing my phone,
因为我设置为静音…
and because I keep my ringer off...
如果有办法找到就好了
It'd be nice if there was a way to find it.
对 但其实很简单 对吗？
Yeah,but apparently,it's pretty simple,right?
- 我没说简单… - GPS？
- I didn't say it was simple... - GPS?
载波信号三角定位？
Carrier signal triangulation?
不是
No.
只要发送一个彩信 附上侵入病毒
Basically,you just send an intrusion virus attached to a picture text
就能把手机从静音改为铃声
that switches the phone from silent to ring.
多数手机会自动安装 因此只要…
Most phones load images automatically,so if you...
假如没有手机信号覆盖呢？
What if there's no cell phone coverage?
假如是小一点的网络的两部手机呢？
If it's two phones on a smaller network?
同样的做法 即使是无线网络
It's the same protocol. Even over Wi-Fi.
你做这种事要多长时间？
How fast could you do something like that?
你是说现在？
What,like right now?
是的
Yes.
这要看情况
There are variables.
手机和网络
The phone and the network.
另一部手机是否开机
If the other phone is even turned on or not.
开机 但手机号匿名
It's on. But the target number is anonymous.
只能从这个手机发送
You have to send it from this phone.
天啊
Jesus.
我不知道这是否合适
Marshal,I don't know about this.
你能做到吗？
Can you do it?
这个人威胁要杀人 他现在能看到我们吗？
This dude is talking about killing people. Can he see us right now?
我就在这里
I'm here.
我可以试一下 但我保证不了…
I guess I can give it a shot. But I can't guarantee...
要多长时间？
How fast?
30分钟？
Thirty minutes?
20分钟？
Twenty?
我们只有不到8分钟
We have less than eight minutes.
你能行的 所以他们才想聘用你 是吧？
You can do it. That's why they want to hire you,right?
8分钟
Eight minutes.
好吧
Okay.
好了跟我说一声
Tell me when it's ready.
谢谢你 女士
Thanks,ma'am.
喂 喂
Hey,hey.
你在驾驶舱看到了什么？
What did you see up there?
我不能说的
I'm really not at liberty to say.
你是医生什么的吗？
What,are you like a doctor or something?
怎么回事？
What the hell?
各位乘客请注意
Ladies and gentlemen,if I can have your attention.
商务舱现在关闭
The business cabin is now closed.
商务舱现在禁止任何人进入
I repeat,the business cabin is now closed to everyone.
空乘人员 请你们尽力
Flight attendants,if you could do your best,
安排所有乘客
please,to accommodate all passengers.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还有家人呢 老天爷啊
I have a family,for Christ's sake!
我们遇到情况
We have a situation.
你到底告不告诉我们出了什么事？
Hey,man,you gonna tell us what the hell is going on or not?
机长情况怎样？
Is the captain all right or not?
这… 这情况很复杂
The... The situation is quite complicated.
复杂？拜托
Complicated? Come on!
但我向你们保证…
But I can assure you...
这是胡闹
This is bullshit!
一切都在控制中
Everything's in hand!
Everything is under control!
大家都镇静
Everyone,calm down!
我要见见机长
I want to see the captain.
我自己去
I'm gonna head up there myself.
受不了了 让开 空警
That's it. Move aside,Marshal.
等等 免费旅行
Wait,wait. Free travel.
免费飞行
Free flights!
免费旅行
Free travel.
航空公司会保证
The airline company will guarantee
为期一年的免费国际旅行
one year's international free travel.
只要你们坐下 保持安静 照我说的做
If you sit down,remain quiet,and do what I say.
免费国际旅行
Free international travel.
谢谢
Thank you.
12个月
Twelve months.
免费
Free.
保证
Guaranteed.
一年 免费旅行 谢谢
One year. Free travel. Thank you.
凯尔 我是比尔
Kyle,it's Bill.
为什么掉头？
Why are we turning?
我被指示不和你交流 马克斯
I've been instructed not to communicate with you,Marks.
他们告诉你切断网络了吗？听我说
Did they tell you to cut the network? Listen to me.
指示你的人不在这飞机上
The men who issued those instructions are not on this plane.
这是你的飞机 他们是你的乘客 赖斯
This is your plane. These are your passengers. Rice!
凯尔
Kyle!
我们转向北方已经55分钟了
We've been diverted north. 55 minutes.
他们告诉你切断网络了吗？
Did they tell you to cut the network?
我有命令在身 马克斯
I have orders,Marks.
给我5分钟 5分钟
Give me five minutes. Five minutes.
你想在哪里降落都可以
Land the plane wherever you want,
但不要切断网络
but do not switch that network off.
听见了吗？我有个计划 我能查出这个人
Do you hear me? I have a plan. I can find this guy.
5分钟
Five minutes.
但愿他能信得过
I hope we can trust this guy.
我信任他
I trust him.
我可不想担上劫机同案犯的罪名
Yeah,well,I'd rather not end up an accessory to a hijacking.
- 好了 - 扎克
- Okay. - Zack.
可以了 给你
It's done. Here it is.
好样的
Good man.
你觉得机长还在控制着飞机吗？
You think the captain's still in control of the plane?
飞机差点坠毁
The plane almost goes down,
这个人挥舞着枪 还绑人
there's a guy waving his gun around,tying people up.
我看是他控制着飞机
I'd say he pretty much took control.
那么国际免费旅行只是他信口开河？
So you think the thing about free international flights was bullshit,or...
我们什么时候才做点什么？
At what point do we do something?
诸位 请回到自己座位上
Gentlemen,would you please return to your seats?
你也不知道什么情况 对吧？
You don't know what's going on either,do you?
那个空警现在要干什么？
So,what's the air marshal up to now?
各位乘客
Ladies and gentlemen,
所有人把手举到头上
I need every passenger to raise their hands above their heads
保持沉默60秒
and remain silent for the next 60 seconds.
这不是请求
This is not a request.
举起来
Up.
也包括乘务人员
Flight attendants,too.
举起来
Up!
发送彩信
是
- 手放在脑后 - 你他妈…
- Hands behind your head. - What the fuck...
手放在脑后
Hands behind your goddamn head!
一只手把手机拿出来
Remove the phone. With one hand.
我从未见过这部手机
I've never seen that phone before.
小姐 解开他的安全带
Miss,undo his seatbelt.
站起来
Stand up,now.
你搜查过我 我的手机在我包里
You searched me. My phone was in my bag.
到过道上
Into the aisle.
不管你以为我做了什么…
Whatever you think I've done...
闭嘴 到飞机前面 走
Shut up. Front of the plane. Move!
你搞错了
You're making a mistake.
转过身
Turn around.
轻点
Take it easy!
怎么回事？
What's going on?
听我说 拜托 这不是我的手机
Listen to me,please! That's not my phone!
你是什么人？
Who are you?
只是个乘客
Just a passenger!
为什么在我的名下开账户？
Why did you open the account in my name?
我不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about!
回答问题 否则扭断你的胳膊
Answer the question,or I will break your arm.
你抓错人了
You got the wrong guy!
我们找到他了 南希 查到他了
We found him,Nancy. We got him.
为什么是我？为什么？
Why me? Why?
为什么是我？
Why me?
为什么？
Why?
南希 叫医生来 快
Nancy,get the doctor. Now!
比尔？比尔？
Bill? Bill?
好 我们分析一下
Okay,let's break this down.
他先是绑了这个人 然后又抓走了另一个人
First,he ties up that guy,then he takes another guy and brings him out back.
他是要一个个的除掉我们吗？
What,is he gonna pick us off one by one?
医生来了 喂
That's the doctor right there. Hey.
你要告诉我们怎么回事了吗？
You want to let us all know what's going on?
- 机长呢？- 死了
- And the captain? - Dead.
副驾驶员在锁着的驾驶舱内驾驶
The co-pilot is flying. Behind locked doors.
- 你怎么样？- 我？我没事 我挺好
- Are you all right? - Me? Fine. I'm great.
不该让你看到这一幕的
You shouldn't be seeing all this.
这么说 死了一个乘客和机长
All right,Doc. So,we got a dead passenger and a dead pilot.
15分钟前飞机急转弯
The plane took a hard turn 15 minutes ago.
这不该在飞行途中发生的
That doesn't happen mid-flight.
空警封锁了商务舱
The marshal closed off business class,
把乘客都赶到后面
moved all the passengers to the back.
这一场景是否似曾相识？
Does this scenario ring any bells?
你觉得他打算让飞机坠毁？
You think he's gonna crash the plane?
10次航班 我是英国空军114号
Flight 10,this is Royal Air Force 114,
呼号长耳大野兔 能收到吗？
call sign Jackrabbit. How copy?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
她们说我可以和丈夫坐在这里
I was told I could stay here with my husband.
当然
Of course.
你1个小时前去过卫生间 还记得吗？
You used the lavatory about an hour ago. Do you remember that?
我并没有老年痴呆症
I don't have Alzheimer's.
你知道随后还有谁进去吗？
Do you know if someone else went in there after you?
是的 她站在那儿挡住了过道
Yes,she was standing there blocking the aisle.
谁？
Who?
那个红发女
The redhead.
坐在你身边的女人
The woman you were sitting next to.
你到这里干什么？
What are you doing in here?
我在喝酒 对不起 这样很不好
I'm drinking. I'm sorry,I shouldn't. That's just terrible.
我在想
I've been wondering.
为何非要靠窗？
Why the window seat?
什么？为何非要靠窗？
What? Why the window seat?
为何要坐在我旁边？
Why did you sit next to me?
- 什么？- 我在商务舱卫生间
- What? - I found a hole
发现一个洞 能直接射中机长
in the first class toilet,clear shot to the captain.
那个死了的人皮肤上有这个
The guy who died had one of these imbedded in his skin.
你见过吗？
Ever seen one before?
没有
No.
机长死前10分钟 卫生间是锁着的
The toilets were locked 10 minutes before the captain died.
此前5分钟 我看到一个女人进去
Five minutes before that,I saw a woman enter.
她70岁了
She's 70 years old.
她说你是随后进去的
She said you went in after her,
另外她也没有老年痴呆症
and she doesn't have Alzheimer's,if you're wondering.
你是问我是否看见别人进去
Are you asking me if I saw someone else go in,
还是问我是否杀了机长呢？
or if I killed the captain?
你看到别人了吗？
Did you see someone else?
没有
No.
那就回答问题
Then answer the question.
你是个混蛋
You're a dick.
你换座位到我身边 博得我的信赖
You switched seats to be next to me,which made you trustworthy.
你和我攀谈
You engaged me in conversation.
为了让你放松 因为你很害怕…
To relax you because you were scared...
可你避开私人问题
Yet you evaded personal questions.
我的工作地点当然是私人问题
You mean,like where I work. Yeah,that's a great personal question.
你主动参与调查
You inserted yourself into the investigation.
你是认真的？
Are you serious?
追踪手机就是你的点子
Tracking the phone,that was your idea.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我是飞机上唯一站在你这边的人
I am the only person on this plane who has stood by you.
而你一直对我撒谎
You've been lying to me this entire time.
你从登机起就对我撒谎
You've been lying to me since the second you boarded this plane.
天啊 好吧 好吧
Oh,God! Okay,fine,fine!
7年前我心脏衰竭
Seven years ago my heart failed,
死亡了43分钟
and I was dead for like 43 minutes.
主动脉弓瘤
Aortic arch aneurysm.
医生试图治疗 但当我醒来
They tried to fix it,but when I woke up,
他们说治不了这个病
they told me it was something they couldn't fix
将来还会复发 然后我就死了
and that one day it would fail again and I would just die.
我无所谓 因为人人将来都会死的
And that's okay with me because we're all gonna die someday,
而且谁也不知道会在哪一天 对吧？
and none of us know when it's gonna be,right?
但当我乘飞机时 经常乘飞机
But when I fly,which is a lot,
我喜欢看着窗外
I like to look out the window instead of
而不是前面的座椅
at the back of the seat in front of me
或是折叠餐桌 因为保不准就死在今天
or a folding tray table,because one day might be today.
你又为何喜欢靠过道座位呢？
Why do you like the aisle?
混蛋
Dick.
等一下
Wait a second.
来
Here.
给你倒一杯真正的酒
Let me pour you a real drink.
谢谢
Thanks.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我讨厌飞行
I hate flying.
是吗？
Really?
我一直挺喜欢的 你知道吗？
I always kind of liked it,you know?
6个小时呆在同一地点 没人能来找你
Six hours in the same spot,nobody can get to you.
无事可做 只是呆在那里 你知道吗？
Nothing to do but just be present,you know?
你真是毫无控制
You have no control.
控制只是假象 不存在控制
Control is an illusion. There is no control.
对任何事
Over anything.
你来听听这个
You need to listen to this.
联邦拆弹小组和调查员正在搜查
Where a federal bomb squad and investigators are searching
一辆据称是比尔·马克斯的汽车
a car that allegedly belongs to Bill Marks.
消息称 在登上英国亚奎兰蒂航空公司10次航班之前
Sources tel! us that Marks parked his car here at the airport today
马克斯把他的车停在机场
before boarding British Aqualantic Flight 10,
他以前多次登机
the way he had boarded so many flights before,
表面是普通乘客
in the guise of an everyday passenger,
其实肩负着
but carrying a mandate
美国国土安全部分派的任务
from the United States Department of Homeland Security.
他的职责是保护航班
His job,to protect the flight.
他也携带一把隐藏的手枪
And he was also,as always,carrying a concealed handgun.
我们知道这是劫机者的手机 能据此查出什么吗？
Well,we know this is the hijacker's phone. Can it tell us anything?
有密码保护 我进不去
It's password protected. I can't get in.
你有没有猜下密码？
Did you try guessing?
这是一架从纽约飞往伦敦的跨大西洋航班
This is a transatlantic flight from New York to London,
航空公司已经确认
the airline now confirming this is,
正在发生劫机
in fact,a hijacking in progress.
- 你做了什么？- 我什么都没做 我对天发誓
- What did you do? - I didn't do anything,I swear to God.
我只是随便摆弄了一下 什么都没做
I just was messing around with it. I didn't do anything.
我是比尔·马克斯
我已没别的选择了
你让我别无选择
已启动
打开客舱中所有的包
Open every bag in this cabin.
可怕的是 这个劫机者
And the horrific twist is that the hijacker
拒信正是这个
is now believed to be the one person who
有权携带枪支上飞机的人
was authorized to carry a gun onto the plane.
你要寻找一个包裹 看到后肯定能认出来
You're looking for a package. You'll know if you find it.
- 每个包 快去 - 好的
- Every bag. Go! Now! - Okay.
麦尼克
Marenick.
- 马克斯？- 命令这架飞机下降到8千英尺
- Marks? - Order this plane down to 8,000 feet.
马克斯 听我说
Marks,listen to me.
我有理由相信飞机上有个炸弹
I have reason to believe there's a bomb on the plane.
- 马克斯 听我说 - 我们需要降低高度
- Agent Marks,just listen to me. - We need to drop altitude now.
这么高的话 炸弹会让飞机散架
A bomb at this height would tear this plane apart.
所有疑问都集中到比尔·马克斯
and questions already swirling around
和他登机时
Bill Marks and his state of mind
的精神状态…
as he boarded the flight...
比尔 你给我发短信说
Bill,when you send me a text and you say
你已没别的选择了 你也知道不是这样的
that you're out of options,you and I both know that's not the case.
还有谁收到这一短信的？
Who else received that message?
显然我们运输安全局是收到了
Clearly,we got it here at TSA.
我们还接到FBI 白宫的电话
We're getting calls from the FBI,the White House,
如今媒体也卷入进来
and now the press is involved.
你已经成功得到了关注 没必要再做别的啥事了
You have our attention. There's no need to take this any further,Bill.
不用再有人死 我知道你感觉没人在聆听你 但我在听
No one else has to die. I know it feels like no one is listening,but I am.
我们好商量
We'll work it out together.
麦尼克 你不懂
Marenick,you're not getting this!
比尔 听我说 我们把事情谈开
Bill,listen to me. Let's talk this through.
听你的口气 仿佛我是恐怖分子
You're talking to me like I'm a terrorist.
你知道规矩
You know how this works.
如果你要把飞机下降到民用空域
If you try to bring that plane any lower into civilian airspace,
你会被击落的
you will be shot down.
你会对地面造成威胁
You're a threat to ground,Bill.
你安稳等着你的钱吧
Just wait for your money and sit tight.
显然是一个处于危险精神状态的人
A stark picture of a man in a dangerous psychological state.
比尔 和我保持通话 你要与我们合作…
Bill,stay with me. I need you to cooperate with us...
现在呢？
What now?
官方称他出身于北爱尔兰
Officials say he was originally from Northern Ireland.
成为一个优秀纽约警察
He became a decorated New York City
有一个年轻的家庭
police officer with a young family.
在他8岁的女儿奥利维亚因癌症病逝时
He became distraught when his 8-year-old daughter,Olivia,
他悲痛欲绝
passed away from cancer.
之后10年 消息称他变得孤僻
Over the next decade,sources say he became withdrawn,
2003年离婚
got divorced in 2003.
被停职 之后被纽约警察局解雇
Suspended and later fired from the NYPD,
然后在2003年夏
it was then,in the summer of 2003,
他被调到联邦空警部门
that he transferred to the Federal Air Marshal Service.
在那里 他的同事和邻居
And there,his colleagues and neighbors
说他很内向 不常与人交往
saying he's a quiet man who kept mostly to himself.
这一部门耗费也很高
This is a costly program,as well.
毫无疑问 让一个精神不稳 充满愤怒的人拥有权力
There's no question. This is what happens when you put an unstable,
就会发生这种事
angry man in a position of power.
此人甚至不是在美国出生的
This guy wasn't even born in the U. S.
他是爱尔兰共和军的都有可能
He could be IRA,for all we know.
谢谢
Thank you.
在911之后 我们在飞机上派了4千名空警
Since 9/11,we've put 4,000 air marshals in the sky.
这些人都来自哪里？
Where do these people come from?
我亲眼见过这种人
I've seen these guys myself.
他们径直走过警戒线
They walk right past the security line
根本不配携带警徽
and they're barely qualified to carry a badge.
径直走过警戒线
Walked right past security.
围绕着空警部门 已经有过不少非议
There's controversy around the air marshal program already.
这次是致命一击吗？
Is this the final blow?
我们让这些人在飞机上拥有特权
We give these people absolute power in the sky.
给他们发枪 让他们到飞机上
We give them guns and we put them on planes,
当出现走私毒品时 我们却惊讶
and we're surprised when we have incidences of drug smuggling.
天啊
Oh,God.
动手
Now!
快 快
Go,go,go!
抓住他 抓住他 夺枪
Grab him! Grab him! Get the gun!
- 帮帮我 - 等等
- Help me,man! - Wait!
住手
Hey,stop it!
- 住手 - 不 不
- Stop it! - No,no,no,no.
趴下
Stay down!
- 打倒他 揍他 - 来人阻止他
- Take him down! Kick his ass! - Somebody stop him.
住手
Stop it!
噢 我的天啊
Oh,my God!
住手
Stop!
帮帮我啊
Help me,man!
放开他
Let go of him!
住手
Stop!
把他按在地上 按住他
Get him to the ground! Hold him steady!
抱住他的腿
Get his legs!
按住他
Hold him,God damn it!
- 抱住他的腿 - 听我说
- Grab his legs! - Listen to me!
- 听我说 - 闭嘴
- Listen to me! - Shut up!
听我说 去卫生间看看
Listen to me,please! Please,go into the bathroom!
- 把他按倒 - 去卫生间看看
- Pin him down! - In the bathroom!
- 你完了 空警 - 里面有具尸体
- You're done,Marshal! - There's a dead body!
闭嘴 闭嘴
Shut the hell up! Shut up!
里面有具尸体和一个手提箱
There's a dead body and a briefcase!
手提箱里有个炸弹
In the briefcase you'll find a bomb!
胡说 你在撒谎
Bullshit,you're lying!
这架飞机上有个炸弹
There is a bomb on this plane.
相信我 拜托
Believe me,please!
放开他
Get off of him.
我让你们放开他 放开他
I said get off of him! Get off him!
快点 退后 退后
Do it now. Get back,back!
你们都退后
Back away,all of you.
你不要拿着枪胡来
You don't know what you're doing with that gun.
拜托 他在干什么？
Come on. What is he doing?
博文 把枪给我
Bowen,give me the gun.
- 汤姆 拜托 - 你站在这里别动
- Tom,please. - No,stay where you are.
我是纽约警察 我们控制了局势 把枪放下
I'm NYPD,we got it covered! Put it down!
飞机上有炸弹吗？
Is there a bomb on this plane?
我要你告诉我是怎么回事
I want you to tell me what the hell is going on.
- 放松 - 别让我放松
- Relax. - Don't tell me to relax!
这航班上有一个乘客
A passenger on board this flight has
他威胁每20分钟杀一个人
threatened to kill someone every 20 minutes
除非他们拿到1.5亿美元
unless they're paid $150 million.
现在已经死了3个人
And now,three people are dead.
那炸弹还有不到半小时就爆炸了
The bomb will explode in less than half an hour.
他们希望你们认为我是嫌疑人
Now,they want you to believe that I'm responsible.
新闻上对我的介绍都是事实
Everything you've heard about me is true.
我失去了家人 工作 我是个酒鬼
I've lost my family,my job. I'm an alcoholic.
我女儿5岁时诊断有急性白血病
My daughter was diagnosed with acute leukemia at the age of five,
而我整天在警局里 却不在家里陪她
and I spent my days at work instead of being at home,
照顾她 因为我害怕看着她死
looking after her,because I was afraid of watching her die!
我不是个好人 不是好父亲
I'm not a good father. I'm not a good man.
我不是打算劫持这架飞机
I'm not hijacking this plane.
我是为了拯救它
I'm trying to save it!
而我肯定能拯救 只要你们与我合作
And I will save it! If you work with me.
你是纽约警察 我也曾经是
You're NYPD. So was I,
感觉你比我当年要强
and you look as if you were a better officer than I was.
给他松绑 南希
Cut him loose. Nancy.
我们需要开始把行李运到后部
We need to start moving all the luggage towards the back.
让妇女和儿童
And move the women and children,
转移到飞机前部
move them up to the front of the plane.
这就是你的计划？
That's your plan?
我的职责是应对最糟糕的情况
My job is to prepare for the worst possible outcome.
我的职责是防止这种情况
Well,my job is to prevent it.
妇女和儿童 没有例外 男人去经济舱
Women and children,no exceptions. Men move up in coach.
你他妈到底在想什么啊？
What the hell are you thinking?
有一个行动预案
There's a plan of action that exists
叫做"最小阻力爆炸位置预案"
called the Least Resistant Bomb Location Protocol.
把炸弹放在后门
You place the bomb against the rear door
上面堆放很多东西
and stack anything and everything against it.
全部的包 毛毯 枕头 尽力抵消爆炸力
Every bag,blanket,every pillow. Nullify it as best you can.
在这个高度 炸弹会让飞机散架
At this height a bomb would tear this plane apart,
但我们下降到8千英尺的话 压力平衡
but we descend to 8,000 feet,pressure equalizes,
那么我们还有机会
and then we have a chance.
那么你就任由炸弹爆炸？
So you're just gonna let the bomb go off?
当然不是 我要阻止它
Of course not,I'm gonna stop it.
但如果阻止不了 还是有所准备的好 不是吗？
But if I can't,I'd rather be prepared,wouldn't you?
把炸弹带上飞机的人不会束手就擒
The man who brought this bomb on the plane may try something.
我能指望你制伏他吗？
Can I trust you to stop him?
你放心就是
You're damn straight you can.
雷利 对不起打断了你的鼻子
Hey,Reilly,sorry about the nose.
反正以前的模样也不好看
It was never my best feature.
你能不能让他们转账？试试办法
Can't you get them to wire the money? Just try something?
他们不是为了钱
This was never about the money.
那么是为了什么？
Then what's it about?
我拿不准 他们用我名下的一个账户
I'm not sure. They used an account in my name.
他们希望一个空警劫持一架飞机
They want an air marshal to take down a plane
劫持150人
with 150 people on board,
他们还想让世人看到这一幕
and they want the whole world to see it.
我本不该找到炸弹的
I was never supposed to find that bomb.
看
Look.
这可不是好事
That's not good.
你知道这意味着什么吗？
Do you know what that means?
亚奎兰蒂航空10次航班 我是英国空军114号
Aqualantic Flight 10,this is Royal Air Force 114,
呼号长耳大野兔 能收到吗？
call sign Jackrabbit. How copy?
收到 长耳大野兔
Copy,Jackrabbit.
我们将护送你去指定降落区
We will be your escorts to the designated landing zone.
不得私自改变
Do not deviate from your current course
目前航线及高度
or altitude without authorization.
- 能收到吗？- 收到
- Do you copy? - Copy.
凯尔
Kyle.
- 凯尔 - 什么？马克斯
- Kyle. - Yes,Marks?
出现了新情况
We have a new situation.
那还用说
Yeah,no shit.
我要你把飞机降到8千英尺高度
I need you to drop the plane to 8,000 feet.
尽量去气压差最小的地方
Get to the lowest pressure deferential you can.
1个大气压 最多1.5个
One PSI,1.5 at most.
等等 比尔 这可是爆炸预案
Wait,Bill,that's explosives protocol.
是的 我们还有16分钟左右
Yes,we have 16 minutes,give or take.
你知道来了别的飞机 是吧？
You know we have company,right?
两架台风喷气机正在我的侧翼
Two typhoons are flanking me right now.
你让我在他们眼皮底下…
They're watching,and you want me to...
凯尔 我们要马上下降高度
Kyle,we need to drop altitude now.
听着 我接到命令 马克斯 有任何可疑举动的话…
Look,I have orders,Marks. Any suspicious activity and they...
赖斯
Rice!
机上有个炸弹 我们必须降到8千英尺
There is a bomb on this plane. We have to descend to 8,000 feet.
好吧 给我10分钟 如果现在下降 我会减速
AH right,give me 10 minutes. If we drop now,I lose speed.
在这个高度10分钟 也许我们就能接近冰岛
Ten minutes at this altitude,maybe I can get us close enough,
可以开始降落到冰岛上
close enough to land in Iceland.
10分钟 谢谢
Ten minutes. Thanks.
这是RDX炸弹 很专业 可能是军方的
It's an RDX explosive. Very professional. Maybe military.
这东西能爆炸？
Is that blow?
你确定能拆除吗？
Are you positive it can't be disarmed?
这是标准压力触发器
This is a calibrated pressure trigger.
拆除炸弹的唯一方式就是拆掉触发器
The only way to disarm a bomb is to remove the trigger.
但拆掉触发器的话 压力释放 炸弹就会爆炸
But remove the trigger,the pressure releases,the bomb goes off.
- 把它扔出去不行吗？- 也是一样的
- Well,can't we just dump it? - Same principle in reverse.
飞机外的低气压
The low pressure outside the plane
维持不了触发器 扔出去的话…
won't hold the trigger. You try to dump it...
炸弹就会爆炸
The bomb goes off.
- 没有什么电线可以切断吗？- 没有
- Isn't there like a wire you can cut? - No.
那么如果这个人拿不到钱
So,if this guy doesn't get his money,
他就把自己和飞机上所有一起炸死？
he's gonna kill himself and everyone aboard?
真不敢相信这种事
I can't believe this. This is crazy.
- 我们为啥不去找这个人呢？- 我们没时间了
- Why aren't we looking for this guy? - We're out of time.
这是荒唐的回答 空警
That's a bullshit answer,Marshal,you know it.
别冲动
Take it easy.
乘客和乘务人员有150个人 说不定是谁
There's 150 passengers and crew. It could be anyone.
我们去找他 给他钱 做点什么
Let's find him! Let's pay him,let's do something.
他不是为了钱 即使我找到了他…
It's not about the money,and even if I find him...
我想他也没打算活着下飞机
I don't think he ever intended to get off this plane.
天啊 我们都要死了
My God,we're all gonna die.
不会
No!
我们要把炸弹放在这里 把所有可用行李堆在上面
We gotta place the bomb here. Stack all available luggage over it.
把爆炸力引向外面
And direct the explosion outward.
在8千英尺高度 内外气压会平衡 然后我们着陆
At 8,000 feet,the pressure will equalize. Then we land.
- 机身有个大洞情况下降落？- 这招奏效过吗？
- With a hole in the fuselage? - And this has worked before?
从未试过这一招
It's never been tried before.
- 试过你也不知道 - 说这些没用 医生
- That you know of. - You're not being helpful,Doctor.
我们死定了
We're so screwed.
有可能成功的 我们必须试试
It could work! We've got to try!
快 让能帮忙的人都来 我们办妥这件事
Come on! Grab every able hand! Let's get this done!
空警 既然他们肯定要引爆炸弹
Marshal,if they're setting this thing off,no matter what,
为何还要等一段时间？
what are they waiting for?
拿上你能拿的东西 去机后
Just grab what you can,go to the back.
你们几个接力
All right,you guys form a chain,
尽快把行李传递过去
send those bags back as fast as you can.
请取出头顶行李舱的所有行李
Please remove all luggage from the overhead bins.
凯尔 我们还有多远？我们现在得马上下降
Kyle,how close are we? We need to descend,now!
不行 给我3分钟时间
No,give me three minutes.
3分钟 好
Three minutes,okay.
看看你的表 3分钟后 1秒也不能耽搁
Look at your watch. Three minutes from now,not a second longer.
无论如何都要下降到8千英尺
No matter what happens,drop down 8,000 feet.
好
Okay.
- 拿着 - 先放轻行李
- Take this. - Lighter luggage up front.
继续堆放 重行李的放下面
Keep piling please. Bring the heavier luggage down.
持续传递
Keep them going.
先生 这个留着 我只需要…
Sir,keep that with you,I just need...
你的鼻子
Your nose.
对 在出血 谢谢
Yeah,it's bleeding,thanks.
有移位性骨折
You have a displaced fracture.
只是鼻子破了而已 很正常 不需要你治疗
Look,it's a broken nose,it's normal,I don't need you to fix it.
我要让你的鼻子复位
Look,I'm going to set your nose.
给 拿着
Here,hold this.
那就快一点 好吗？
Just make it quick,all right?
施点压力
Apply some pressure.
好
Okay.
数3下 1…
On three. One...
孩子 你必须出来
Sweetheart,you've got to come out.
没事的 我会拉着你的手 这里不安全
It's all right,I'll hold your hand. But it's not safe.
- 格温 怎么了？- 拜托
- Gwen,what's going on? - Please.
我们得快点
We need to hurry.
对不起 我需要你帮忙 她不肯出来
Sorry. I'm sorry,I need your help. She won't come out.
怎么了？你害怕？
What's wrong? Are you scared?
我想见爸爸
I wanna see my daddy.
我知道 孩子 我知道
I know you do,sweetheart. I know you do.
我也曾是你这样的小姑娘的爸爸
You know,I was a daddy once to a little girl just like you,
当她害怕时 你知道她做什么吗？
and when she was scared,you know what she'd do?
她有个魔法丝带 法力强大
She had a magic ribbon,very powerful.
它能保护你 就像你爸爸一样
It'll protect you,just like your daddy.
你想看看吗？就在我的口袋里
You wanna see it? I have it in my pocket.
我一直随身带着 给
I carry it all the time. Here it is. Here.
绕在手上 像这样
You wrap it around your hand,just like that.
对 现在把它攥紧了
That's it,hold on to it now.
你是想收买我吗？
Are you bribing me?
是的
Yes,I am.
这是我朋友珍妮 她会照顾你的
This is my friend,Jen. She's gonna look after you.
- 珍妮 这是贝嘉 - 你好
- Jen,this is Becca. - Hey.
放心 你会很快见到爸爸 我保证
Don't worry,you'll see your father soon. I promise.
我能坐在靠窗的座位吗？
Can I have the window seat?
你是说这个老旧的座位？嗯哼
You mean this old seat? Mm-hm.
各位乘客 我们就要开始下降了
Ladies and gentlemen,we 're about to begin our descent.
请你们回到座位上 系紧安全带
I need you to return to your seats and fasten your seatbelts.
请各位保持镇静 回到自己座位上
Please stay calm. Everyone,please get back to your seats.
喂
Yeah?
马克斯 我们已经转账
Marks,we transferred the money,
1.5亿美元已经到了你的账户
150 million US into your account.
现在转账来不及了 不管他目的何在…
It's too late for the money. Whatever he's doing...
你可以收手了 马克斯 你已经拿到了钱
You can stop now,Marks. You have your money.
喷气机会护送你降落
The jets will escort you in.
我必须让飞机下降到8千英尺
I have to bring this plane down to 8,000 feet.
你不能下降到民用空域
You will not descend into civilian airspace.
你以为他要的是钱？你以为这就能让他收手？
You think he wants the money? You think that will stop him?
如果你已经转账 证明一下
If you transferred the money,prove it.
你要证明？给你证明 1.5亿美元
You want proof? Here's your proof,$150 million was transferred
已转至账户CH 1000 23000 A 10982
to account CH-1000-23000-A-10982.
确认码 R48940
Confirmation code R48940.
我们会护送你进入军用空域
We'll escort you into a military air field,
不会逮捕你 也不会问你什么
you will not be arrested,no questions will be asked.
机上有个炸弹 不是我的 肯定会爆炸
There is a bomb on this plane. It isn't mine. It will go off!
- 我们要应对… - 你控制着一架被劫持客机
- And we have to prepare... - You're in command of a hijacked vessel
你不得把飞机下降到民用空域
and you will not dive that plane into civilian airspace.
我会的
I will!
那么我们就击落你
Then,Marks,God damn it,we will shoot you down!
等将来 会有人从大西洋底打捞出飞机的黑匣子
Someday,they'll fish this plane's black box out of the Atlantic Ocean,
世人就会知道这些人本可免于一死
and the world will know these people could have been saved.
世人已经知道飞机上的事
The world already knows what's going on
比尔 你劫持了飞机
in that plane,Bill. You are hijacking it.
- 那是你这么说的 - 不 不 不
- That's what you're telling them. - No,no,no,no,no.
这是你的人质说的
That's what your hostages are telling them.
那段视频正在各大新闻网反复播放
That video is playing on every major news network on repeat,Bill.
- 什么视频？- 你的一名人质上传的视频
- What video? - One of your hostages uploaded a video.
你抓了个人 拿枪顶着他
You're taking a man,dragging him around at gunpoint,
在害怕的乘客中走过去
stumbling over terrified passengers.
我们还怎么相信你的话
How do you expect us to believe anything that you're saying
你显然在虐待人质嘛
when you clearly are abusing those hostages?
我们都已经看到了
We've seen everything we need to know.
可我们依然和你协商…
But we're trying to negotiate...
你的手机 交出来
Your phone,now! The phone!
让我看看你上传的视频 快
Show me the video that you uploaded! Come on!
我代儿子道歉
I apologize for my son.
帮我看一下
Humor me. Look!
- 看 - 我没看到他
- Look. - I don't see him.
看看
Come on,look.
- 在那里 - 哪里？
- Right there. - Where?
那个戴眼镜的 快点 过去
Glasses. Come on,move.
该死的
God damn it!
你 看着我…
You. Look...
该死的
God damn it!
别过来
Stay where you are.
比尔 别把我逼急了
Bill,don't test me!
比尔
Bill.
雷利 低头
Reilly,drop!
雷利 趴下
Reilly,get down!
你给我没子弹的枪？
You gave me an unloaded weapon?
舱顶行李箱 4B
Overhead bin,4B!
大家都趴下
Everybody,down! Stay down!
- 嘿 离开那 让开 - 什么？
- Hey,get out of there,move! - What?
嘿 伙计
Hey,man!
你在找它吗？
You looking for this?
给我
Give me that.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
- 后退 - 好 好
- Get back! - Okay,okay.
长耳大野兔 驾驶舱外有枪声 需要下降
Jackrabbit,I have shots fired outside this cockpit,need to descend.
不行 10次航班 不得改变目前航线及高度
That's a negative,Flight 10,do not deviate from your current course or altitude.
转身
Turn around.
你们都把手
I need all of you to put your hands
放在前面的座位上
on the seat-back in front of you.
照做
Do it now!
- 走 - 别惹火了我
- Move. - Don't test me.
后退
Step back!
把手抬起来
Put your hands up!
坐下
Sit!
Sit,sit!
他本来是坐在我旁边的
He was supposed to be in the seat next to mine.
是的 但也不远
Yeah. He was close enough.
听我说 不管我哪里对不起你 我表示道歉
Listen,whatever I've done to you,whatever it is,I'm sorry.
老实坐下
Stay down!
比尔 我不是生你的气
Bill,I'm not mad at you.
你是我的偶像
You're my hero.
世界各处的人都将记得比尔·马克斯这个名字
People everywhere are gonna remember the name Bill Marks.
一个持有枪和警徽的
An alcoholic,self-destructive,
自暴自弃的酒鬼
suicidal man with a gun and a federal badge
改变了一切
who changed everything.
你这样做又能改变什么呢？
What do you think doing this is gonna change?
还有两分钟 穿好
Two minutes outside the window. Suit up.
每个上这个飞机的人
Every one of these people boarded this plane
相信国家能保护他们
believing their country would protect them.
相信你能保护他们
That you would protect them.
"各位"
Everyone!
"我们不会有事的"
We're gonna be okay!
"飞机上有个空警"
There's an air marshal on board.
你知道说这话有多么轻松吗？
Do you have any idea how easy this was?
你说得对 我失败了 你证明了你的观点
You're right,I failed. You've made your point.
不 比尔 你是惨败
No,Bill,you failed miserably!
那天死了3千人 包括我父亲
Three thousand people died that day,including my father!
于是我参军 因为我想与恐怖分子作战
So I joined up 'cause I wanted to go fight the cowards that did it.
可我却参加了一场至今也无法理解的战争
But I just ended up fighting in a war that I still don't understand
回国之后 这个国家也没有任何改变
and came home to a country where nothing had changed.
但今后不同了
Until now.
安保是这个国家最大的谎言
Security is this country's biggest lie.
在我们的家里 城市里 飞机上 没人是安全的
In our homes,in our cities,in our planes,no one's safe,
将来会有比我更狠的人揭露这一谎言
and one day somebody worse than me is gonna expose that lie,
我们的后代最后看到的
and the last thing our children will see
就是我们的失败毁灭了他们
is our failure as it destroys them.
你 比尔 你就是这个谎言
You,Bill,you are that lie!
你散发传单就是了
You should just have handed out pamphlets.
那样简单得多
It would have been a lot easier.
言语是无法改变世界的
You can't change the world with words,Bill,
除非是用鲜血写成的
unless you write those words in the evening news with blood.
我们必须走了
We gotta go.
你们是军人 他们是你们该保护的人
You're military. These are the people you fought to protect.
我的誓言是保护国家 这也是我正在做的
I swore to protect my country,and that's what I'm doing.
- 这话你信？- 我信
- You believe that? - I do.
我也相信我们会赚到1.5亿美元
I also believe we'll be $150 million richer.
你们拿不到那笔钱 账户是在我的名下
You'll never get that money. It's in an account in my name.
是你名下的托管账户
It's in a trust in your name.
我一死 这钱就转移
I die,the money moves.
转移到27个国家的100个账户
To 100 accounts,27 countries,
其中每个账户再转移到100个账户中
each of those into 100 other accounts.
你们打算什么时候跳机？
When do you think you're gonna jump?
在3.5万英尺高度 你们4秒内就会死亡
35,000 feet? You'll be dead in four seconds.
等飞行员启动爆炸预案 下降到8千英尺时
We'll jump when the pilot follows explosive protocol
我们就跳机
and drops us down to 8,000 feet.
你所能想到的 我们都考虑过无数次了
Anything you think of,we've thought of a thousand times.
如果我们下降的话 他们有命令击落我们
They've been instructed to shoot us down if we try to descend.
这是扯淡
That's bullshit!
他们不会杀了这些人的
They're not gonna kill all these people.
这是被劫持的客机 我们对地面有重大威胁
This is a hijacked flight. We're a classified threat to ground.
不拆除炸弹的话 机上人人都会死 包括你们
If you don't disarm that bomb,everyone on board will die,including you.
你们考虑到这一点了吗？
Did you think of that?
- 我已准备好去死 - 我们不会死的
- Look,I'm prepared to die. - We're not gonna die.
再说一遍 长耳大野兔 我需要下降
Say again,Jackrabbit. I need to descend.
不行 10次航班
That's a negative,Flight 10.
我们按原计划 下降 跳机
I'm gonna stick with the plan. We descend,we jump.
飞机坠毁 我们有足够的钱
The plane goes down,we have enough money.
想干什么都可以
We can do whatever we want.
想想吧 汤姆 我们可以人间蒸发 再也不回来
Think about it,Tommy. We can disappear and never come back.
你听见吗？没人找得到我们 永远 任务完成 对吧？
You hear me? Never be found,ever. Mission accomplished,right?
但现在 我们要离开这架飞机
But right now we need to get the hell off this plane.
扎克 你也清楚我们是下不了这架飞机的
Zack,you and I both know we were never getting off this plane.
扎克 不管你真名叫什么 你不必送死
Zack,whatever your name is,you don't have to die.
就算你不愿救这些人 也救救自己
If you won't save these people,save yourself.
拆除炸弹
Disarm the bomb.
快啊
Come on,do it.
他是个殉道者 就像你我一样 比尔
He was a martyr,like you and me,Bill.
真正的英雄不需要被人记住或承认
Real heroes don't need to be remembered or recognized.
真正的英雄做任何必要的事
Real heroes do whatever's necessary.
看来我不会理解了
I guess I wouldn't understand.
- 不管了 - 看来你不会
- Fuck it! - I guess you wouldn't.
不
No!
两万英尺 快点 你这混蛋
20,000! Come on,you wanker!
8千英尺 快 快
8,000 feet! Come on,come on!
比尔
Bill!
8千英尺
8,000!
- 10次航班 爬回2.5万英尺 - 机上有炸弹
- AQ 10,climb back up to 25,000 feet! - There's a bomb on board!
我需要让飞机着陆
I need to get this plane on the ground.
南希 快走 大家都趴下 低头
Nancy,move,move! Everybody down,heads down!
喂 比尔
Hey. Bill!
我要下飞机
I'm getting off this plane!
我挡了你的路？混蛋
Am I in your way,asshole?
趴下
Get down!
快点 低头
Do it quick! Heads down!
趴下
Get down!
加油 凯尔 你能行的 你能行的 加油
Come on,Kyle! You can do this! You can do this,come on.
你的机身严重受损
severe damage to your fuselage.
你能保持控制吗？
Are you able to maintain control?
该死
Shit!
燃油倾泻中
Fuel dump in progress.
- 收到 10次航班 - 加油 该死的
- Copy that,Flight 10. - Come on,damn it!
距离再长一点 加油
A little longer,come on!
天啊
Oh,God!
解开安全带 解开安全带
Get the belt! Get the belt!
- 抓住 - 比尔 救救我
- Hang on! - Bill,help me!
贝嘉 我抓住你了
Becca,I have you!
抓紧我 抓紧我
Hang onto me! Hang onto me!
你还好吧？你没事吧？
You okay? Are you okay?
- 舱门已拆下 - 解开安全带
- Door is disarmed. - Release your seatbelts!
- 带她走 各位 - 跟我来
- Take her. Everybody. - Come on with me.
解开安全带 到前面去 快
Undo your seatbelt! Move to the front,quickly.
什么也不要带 这里来 到前面去
Leave everything. Come this way,up to the front.
一个一个来
One at a time,please.
什么也不要带
Leave everything.
去前面
Up to the front.
什么也不要带
Leave everything.
所有乘客和乘务人员都在这里了
All passengers and crew accounted for.
你呢 你怎么样？
And you,are you all right?
这次着陆真是厉害
That was a hell of a landing.
不到一小时前 英国亚奎兰蒂航空公司10次航班
Less than one hour ago,British Aqualantic Flight 10
在空中炸弹爆炸后 紧急迫降
made an emergency landing after a bomb exploded mid-air.
这是发生在一起劫机未遂案之后 但情节极为曲折
This following an attempted hijacking,yet in an unbelievable twist,
劫机嫌疑犯美国空警比尔·马克斯
the suspected hijacker,U.S. Air Marshal Bill Marks,
原来是英雄
turned out to be the hero.
是马克斯对抗并杀死了劫机犯
It was Marks who confronted and killed the hijackers,
拯救了…
saving the lives...
- 喂 - 我是麦尼克
- Yeah? - It's Marenick.
现在轮到我违反规定了
It's my turn to break protocol,Agent Marks.
我这是用私人线路打的电话
I'm calling from my personal line
我也会否认说过下面的话
and I'll deny this conversation ever took place.
听着 比尔 不管你在机上做了什么 面临了什么情况
Listen,Bill,what you did on that plane,what you were up against,
我想告诉你 我看错你了
I want you to know I was wrong about you.
我会全力维护你的
And you'll have my full support.
谢谢了
Appreciate that.
另外 比尔
And,Bill,
我们要收回那笔钱
we're gonna need that money back.
什么钱？
What money?
保重 马克斯特工
Take care,Agent Marks.
空警
Marshal!
雷利 你这混蛋
Reilly,you son of a gun.
下次给我有子弹的枪
Next time,give me a loaded weapon.
下次要躲开子弹
Next time,don't get shot.
好的
Deal.
我要把你的丝带还给你
I'm gonna give you back your ribbon.
我不再需要它了
I don't need it anymore.
好孩子
That-a-girl.
你爸爸的电话
It's your dad.
爸爸
Daddy.
- 嘿 我正找你呢 - 嘿
- Hey,I was looking for you! - Hey.
- 你知道这是哪里吗？- 冰岛
- Do you know where we are? - Iceland.
噢 从没来过冰岛
Ah! Well,never been to Iceland.
我是说 我在飞机上见过几次 不过…
I mean,I've seen it,few times from plane windows,but...
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢什么？
For what?
你一直站在我这边 不管发生了什么事
You stood by me,even after all that happened.
为什么？
Why?
你是个好人
You're a good man.
你女儿肯定也会为你自豪的
I bet your daughter would have been proud of you.
谢谢你 女士
Thanks,ma'am.
那么…
So...
嗯
Mm-hm.
你要去哪里？
Where you headed?
看情况
Depends.